<u>Р</u> R

# PRITIKA ROY

### FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER



www.pritikaroy.com



Pritikaroy@gmail.com



+1-647-978-7769



Toronto, ON, M5V3Z7, Canada



www.linkedin.com/in/pritikaroy

#### SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS/SASS/Styled Components
- JavaScript/jQuery
- React
- Firebase
- Rest API
- Github/NPM
- Accessibility

#### EDUCATION

#### CERTIFICATE-WEB DEVELOPMENT IMMERSIVE

Juno College of Technology (Formerly HackerYou)

July 2019 – Oct 2019

## POSTGRADUATE ONTARIO GRADUATE CERTIFICATE IN EVENT MANAGEMENT

Humber College Institute of Technology

2014 - 2015

BACHELOR OF ARTS, HONORS BUSINESS MANAGEMENT

Staffordshire University, United Kingdom

2009 - 2012

#### PROFILE

Pritika is a passionate Web Developer by day and an enthusiastic Event Planner by night. In her previous life she engaged in a professional background of Event, Project & Business Management. Her voyage into the world of web development started with coding a static website for her own her company PRitzy Events. This glimmered a curiosity to solve glitches on a whole diverse dimension of coding. As a graduate of the Web Development Immersive Program at Juno (HackerYou) College of Technology, Pritika is fueled by the innate inquisitiveness to solve puzzles seamlessly blending her au natural talent to have an eye for engaging user experiences on a digital level.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **FOUNDER**

PRitzy Events / Toronto, ON / Aug 2018 - May 2019

- Harmonized development, production & delivery of 34 projects from proposal right up to delivery.
- Piloted, maintained & developed positive client relationships.
- Augmented operational & administrative functions to ensure 98% of projects were delivered efficiently.
- Supervised leadership, motivation, direction & support to a team of 10.
- Enabled on-site inspections, chaired for all project budgets from inception to execution.
- Engineered all events on time, attained 10% savings within budget.

#### **EVENT MANAGER**

IQPC-Worldwide Business Research / Toronto, ON / Jan 2016 – June 2018

- Planned, administered over 10 conference operations.
- Administered event incidents & acted swiftly to resolve glitches.
- Excelled in bringing in USD 8000 15,000 worth of business.
- Delegated acquisition & induced working relationships with over 50 senior-level stakeholders: From CEOs to Director Level.
- Spearheaded unified Client Relationship Management.
- Executed over 15 conferences outdoing financial goals by 25%.

#### PROJECT EXECUTIVE

Marcus Evans Group / Toronto, ON / June 2015 – Dec 2015

- Researched, developed over 85% leads, conducted detailed industry analysis & investigated existing trends.
- Identified & contacted key decision makers (C---Level Executives) in legal, finance, pharmaceutical, electric industries to engage them to attend conferences.
- Maintained 120+ call rate on a daily basis.
- Excelled in bringing in USD 10,000 worth of business.